[{"answer": "I think it's a change of generations more than the difference of culture.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "What is the collective mood at the moment?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "I think gossiping is a bad thing.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "What was your reaction when you heard about this?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "You know, when I judge by his actions he really has shown friendship.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Are you confident that you have President Obama's full hundred percent support?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think that this is a correct interpretation of what I have said.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "I mean, how serious should we be taking your comments?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "I think in the beginning most of the leaders thought that it would take a longer period of time before they'll have a bomb.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "When you have somebody in his position with his kind of power apparently are getting nearer and nearer to a nuclear capability, are you surprised that more leaders around the world are not making a more concerted effort to get rid of him, to enforce regime change?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Israel fails to foresee what the world is doing.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Could you foresee a situation where Israel may take military action without the whole support of the United Nations or indeed America?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "I think they've created a mistake, but mistakes are being done by many people.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "He would concentrate on this issue as the main topic.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "What do you think he would have made of the fact that there is still no settlement with the Palestinians so long after he started this process?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Oh, I think it's very clear.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "What is the definition of news in the modern age, do you think?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "I see our chief foreign correspondent Richard Engel in our building when he's in this country.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Has it been exceptional?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, and no false modesty here either.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Tell me about that unique place that you have as a news anchor in America?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Are you a news adrenaline junkie?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "It's the most disturbing story in so long that we've come across, Piers.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Are you pleased with this new addition to the armory?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "If a candidate walked into our offices with her academic training, with her travel, with her access and time around conversations at the highest levels with policy makers, with her business experience, with just her travel experience, we would sit down if their name was Nancy, and have a thorough conversation about coming to work for us at NBC News.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "What would you say to that?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "No, sir, I've never struggled with that at all.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Have you struggled to sleep at night with the idea that any one of those might have been innocent?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "We are.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "We are in extraordinary times, aren't we?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Well, in my -- thank you for saying that.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "What do you think's gone wrong with the American business model?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I'm -- I don't -- I never know what to say about this.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "You like this kind of stuff, don't you?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Just my favorite thing about you -- in addition to the title graphic which shows you in that room with so many dust particles.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "I'm told that one of your numerous comedic talents is you do a very good impression of me?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Once and I remain there.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "But how many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "If we're leaving aside marriage and birth of children and things like that, I would have to say, because it has defined me and it gives me the job title on my business card -- I would have to say taking this job when Tom Brokaw stepped down, because it was so unlikely, because of my very modest circumstances growing up, dropping out of school, kicking around and really not showing any promise.", "docId": "111114pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "What has been the greatest moment of your life, of all the things you've been involved with, that you witnessed, everything?", "qSentId": 478}]